Michael Emborsky

3247 NE Taylor St • Minneapolis, MN 55418 • (716) – 870 – 7734 • <u>michaelemborsky@gmail.com</u>
<u>LinkedIn</u> <u>GitHub</u> <u>Personal Website</u>

Career Objective

Through a range of diverse experiences living overseas, I have developed and refined the ability to be exceedingly adaptive and to connect with and learn from others. Following these years overseas, I have found myself with new entrepreneurial energy and motivation to create and think outside of the box. I have a passion for primarily creative programming opportunities, especially relating to audio design.

Education

Bachelor of Computer Science, concentration in Digital Arts (Graduated Fall 2023)

University of North Carolina, Wilmington

Associate of Science (2020)
Cape Fear Community College

2 Year International Baccalaureate Diploma (2014-2016)

American Community School of Abu Dhabi, Abu Dhabi, U.A.E

Work Experience

Atomic Data – Client Support Specialist (August 2024 – Present) Minneapolis, MN

- Assisting 90+ clients of Atomic Data with tech related problems, including hardware/software troubleshooting, network issues and 0365/email access.
- Working in a call queue, managing tickets, utilizing time entries and sheets.

StuFlo – Software Developer (July 2024 – December 2024) Remote, Internship

- Worked collaboratively with a team of developers with Github to develop a time management app for students.
- Implemented swift code to add and read from a database and SwiftUI code for elaborate designs and views.

Technical Skills

- Python and Java
- HTML, CSS, and JavaScript
- Experience with Swift, SwiftUI, C++, F#, SML, Prolog, Github
- Photoshop, Illustrator, Premiere Pro and After Effects
- FL Studio and Pro Tools

Projects

SoundScape

Platform: Windows, Mac Application
Language: C++
(In Development)
A desktop application for Mac and Windows
that allows for the full customization of a
user's sound elements/inputs.

Lotus State Website

Platform: Website Languages: HTML, CSS, JavaScript A live website for my artist profile, Lotus State. Features immersive animations produced with Javascript, SVGs and queries.

myCloset

Platform: iOS Application Language: Swift

An iOS application that allows for a user to upload, save, and create collages of clothing items and share them with their followers.